Xu.
شو.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
You were never ordinary.
لم تكن شخصاً عادياً أبداً.
Who gave you the right to touch her?
من أعطاك الحق في لمسها؟
Because of this woman,
بفضل هذه المرأة،
you lost yourself.
لقد فقدت نفسك.
You turned into a love-struck idiot
لقد تحولت إلى أحمق مغرم
and destroyed every promise we made.
ودمر كل وعد قطعناه.
What promise?
أي وعد؟
You forgot?
هل نسيت؟
The day we met.
يوم لقائنا.
I could not take the excessive training,
لم أستطع تحمل التدريب المفرط،
being monitored like a prisoner every day,
يخضع للمراقبة كالسجين يومياً،
so I broke down and wanted to end it all.
لذا انهرت وأردت إنهاء كل شيء.
But then I ran into you while you were escaping.
لكنني صادفتك أثناء هروبك.
You are not allowed to die here.
لا يُسمح لك بالموت هنا.
Why?
لماذا؟
Unknown massive life form detected. Area is dangerous.
تم رصد كائن حي ضخم غير معروف. المنطقة خطرة.
Emergency return.
العودة الطارئة.
I can't believe it!
لا أصدق ذلك!
We really escaped that place!
لقد هربنا من ذلك المكان حقاً!
No one has found this place.
لم يعثر أحد على هذا المكان.
If you want to do it, go ahead.
إذا كنت ترغب في القيام بذلك، فافعل.
I do not want to die anymore.
لا أريد أن أموت بعد الآن.
Where are you heading?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Take me with you.
خذني معك.
I'm the strongest in this team.
أنا الأقوى في هذا الفريق.
Everyone calls me Max.
الجميع يناديني ماكس.
I can definitely help you.
بالتأكيد أستطيع مساعدتك.
No.
لا.
You are as annoying as those Yin from the Administration Bureau.
أنت مزعج مثل أولئك الين من مكتب الإدارة.
If you hate Yin that much,
إذا كنت تكره الين إلى هذا الحد،
why don't we create a world
لماذا لا نخلق عالماً
controlled entirely by Ren?
هل يسيطر عليها رين بالكامل؟
You are that strong.
أنت قويٌّ إلى هذا الحد.
You can do it.
بإمكانك فعلها.
I will get stronger too and keep up with you.
سأصبح أقوى أيضاً وسأواكبك.
Let us start now.
لنبدأ الآن.
Stop following my path.
توقف عن اتباع طريقي.
I'll go north. You go south.
سأذهب شمالاً. اذهب أنت جنوباً.
That was when I made up my mind.
عندها اتخذت قراري.
Xu,
شو،
I will meet you at the summit.
سأقابلك عند القمة.
But
لكن
after I cleared every path for you,
بعد أن مهدت لك كل الطرق،
you killed the ideal version of yourself.
لقد قتلت النسخة المثالية من نفسك.
You crushed all of my expectations!
لقد فاق كل توقعاتي!
Since you are no longer who you were,
بما أنك لم تعد الشخص الذي كنت عليه،
then just die!
ثم مت!
I do not need your expectations.
لست بحاجة إلى توقعاتك.
We were never on the same path.
لم نكن نسير على نفس الدرب أبداً.
What I want to destroy
ما أريد تدميره
is the inequality imposed upon Ren,
هل عدم المساواة المفروضة على رين؟
not creating new inequality
عدم خلق عدم مساواة جديدة
like what you're doing.
أعجبني ما تفعله.
♪So no one can find you♪
♪حتى لا يتمكن أحد من العثور عليك♪
♪But still it begins♪
♪لكنها لا تزال تبدأ♪
♪And so it is♪
♪وهكذا يكون الأمر♪
So it turns out
وهكذا اتضح
you never needed me.
لم تكن بحاجة إليّ أبداً.
How dare you touch him?
كيف تجرؤ على لمسه؟
We can make Xuyan a thriving company,
بإمكاننا أن نجعل من شركة شويان شركة مزدهرة.
fulfilling our dream
تحقيق حلمنا
of building a world ruled by Ren.
بناء عالم يحكمه رين.
So all of this
كل هذا
was just my own delusion.
كان ذلك مجرد وهم من صنع خيالي.
If I go on living,
إذا استمررت في الحياة،
what for?
لماذا؟
♪Oh to find light inside of them♪
♪يا ليتني أجد النور في داخلهم♪
♪Flying gets harder as you fall♪
♪يصبح الطيران أصعب كلما سقطت♪
♪Gravity holds no weight at all♪
♪الجاذبية لا تحمل أي وزن على الإطلاق♪
♪When help eludes you♪
♪عندما يفلت منك العون♪
♪Call on love…♪
♪استدعِ الحب…♪
Then, leave me here.
ثم اتركني هنا.
No one has found this place.
لم يعثر أحد على هذا المكان.
If you want to do it, go ahead.
إذا كنت ترغب في القيام بذلك، فافعل.
♪Living for dreams♪
♪نعيش من أجل الأحلام♪
♪Or so it seems♪
♪أو هكذا يبدو♪
♪They come, then they leave you♪
يأتون، ثم يرحلون عنك.
♪Fighting for things♪
♪نقاتل من أجل الأشياء♪
♪So far unseen♪
♪لم يُرَ مثله من قبل♪
♪But sure to appease you♪
♪لكنها سترضيك بالتأكيد♪
♪Hold out your fragile paper heart♪
♪أخرج قلبك الورقي الهش♪
♪Hope for the first time♪
♪أمل لأول مرة♪
♪It will start to heal all on its own♪
♪سيبدأ بالشفاء من تلقاء نفسه♪
♪Like waving candles in the rain♪
♪كأنك تلوح بالشموع تحت المطر♪
♪Yet so surprised to see the flame has gone out once more♪
♪لكنني مندهش للغاية لرؤية أن الشعلة قد انطفأت مرة أخرى♪
♪The flame has gone out once more♪
♪انطفأت الشعلة مرة أخرى♪
♪Only on love♪
♪فقط على الحب♪
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Your hand.
يدك.
This watch monitors your health in real time.
تراقب هذه الساعة صحتك في الوقت الفعلي.
I have one too.
لدي واحدة أيضاً.
If your condition shows anything abnormal,
إذا أظهرت حالتك أي شيء غير طبيعي،
it will send me your location immediately.
سيرسل لي موقعك على الفور.
So, you will be tracking me around the clock?
إذن، ستراقبني على مدار الساعة؟
You got lucky this time.
لقد حالفك الحظ هذه المرة.
Li Xiang and Lin Juan made it in time
وصل لي شيانغ ولين جوان في الوقت المناسب
and got you to the hospital.
ونقلك إلى المستشفى.
You were fortunate,
لقد كنت محظوظاً،
as there are only a few scratches.
حيث لا يوجد سوى خدوش قليلة.
By the way, Siyuan,
بالمناسبة، سيوان،
where is Xie Xinxu?
أين هو شيه شينكسو؟
He just came out of surgery. They got the bullet out.
لقد خرج لتوه من غرفة العمليات. لقد أخرجوا الرصاصة.
He is resting in another ward.
وهو يستريح في جناح آخر.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
you aren't allowed to go on missions with him.
لا يُسمح لك بالذهاب في مهمات معه.
But I handled this one really well.
لكنني تعاملت مع هذا الأمر بشكل جيد للغاية.
For those missing people, Xuyan Trading...
بالنسبة للمفقودين، شركة شويان للتجارة...
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Lin Juan already reported it.
لقد أبلغت لين جوان عن ذلك بالفعل.
There is one thing Lin Juan does not know.
هناك شيء واحد لا تعرفه لين جوان.
Dragons
التنانين
did not go completely extinct.
لم تنقرض تماماً.
There is still one.
لا يزال هناك واحد.
I saw it myself.
رأيت ذلك بنفسي.
I told you before.
لقد أخبرتك من قبل.
I would give you the best of everything.
سأقدم لك أفضل ما في كل شيء.
I went to a lot of trouble
لقد تكبدت الكثير من المتاعب
to recreate this dragon from fossils.
لإعادة إنشاء هذا التنين من الأحافير.
This biological weapon...
هذا السلاح البيولوجي...
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
Are you not worried
ألا تشعر بالقلق؟
that I could tame it, control it, and have it kill you?
هل يمكنني ترويضه، والسيطرة عليه، وجعله يقتلك؟
Get to work.
ابدأ العمل.
Yes.
نعم.
The world is full of strange things.
العالم مليء بالأشياء الغريبة.
Back when you were at Genus,
في ذلك الوقت الذي كنت فيه في شركة جينوس،
did you not see Nan Xing's mutated octopus?
ألم ترَ الأخطبوط المتحول الخاص بنان شينغ؟
But an octopus is not a dragon.
لكن الأخطبوط ليس تنينًا.
The wound looks like it is healing fast.
يبدو أن الجرح يلتئم بسرعة.
If I mess with it like this,
إذا عبثت به بهذه الطريقة،
it will not heal so quickly.
لن يشفى بهذه السرعة.
Is this my reward for grinding through that mission?
هل هذه مكافأتي على إتمام تلك المهمة بصعوبة؟
Why does it look worse again?
لماذا يبدو الأمر أسوأ مرة أخرى؟
It is fine.
لا بأس.
I probably pulled the wound by accident.
ربما قمت بسحب الجرح عن طريق الخطأ.
From now on, do not take solo missions.
من الآن فصاعدًا، لا تقم بمهام فردية.
Stay with me.
ابقى معي.
This knife is for eating,
هذا السكين مخصص للأكل،
not for violent use like that.
ليس للاستخدام العنيف من هذا القبيل.
It is dirty.
إنه مكان قذر.
I'll take it to the dry cleaners later.
سآخذها إلى محل التنظيف الجاف لاحقاً.
I promise you can hold it while you sleep tonight.
أعدك أنك ستتمكن من الاحتفاظ به أثناء نومك الليلة.
My sister has been asking for this every day.
أختي تطلب هذا كل يوم.
I do not get what is so special about it.
لا أفهم ما هو المميز فيه.
Try it.
جربها.
If you are eating cake, just eat it.
إذا كنت تأكل الكعكة، فتناولها فحسب.
Why are you grinning like that?
لماذا تبتسم هكذا؟
It tastes pretty good.
طعمه لذيذ جداً.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
This is your reward
هذه هي مكافأتك
for always remembering to buy cake to cheer me up all these years.
لأنك كنت تتذكر دائماً شراء الكعك لإسعادي طوال هذه السنوات.
I hope you do not misunderstand
أتمنى ألا تسيء فهمي
our relationship.
علاقتنا.
And one more thing.
وشيء آخر.
Do not pull any tricks
لا تقم بأي حيل
behind my back.
من وراء ظهري.
If something happens to you,
إذا حدث لك مكروه،
it'll be a lot of trouble for me too.
سيكون ذلك مصدر إزعاج كبير لي أيضاً.
Got it.
فهمتها.
I will take better care of myself.
سأعتني بنفسي بشكل أفضل.
♪You had a dream inside your head♪
♪كان لديك حلم في رأسك♪
♪Wrote the story's end♪
♪كتبتُ نهاية القصة♪
♪But wrote it in the sand♪
♪لكنها كُتبت على الرمال♪
♪The face in your fairy tale looked like me♪
♪الوجه في حكايتك الخيالية يشبهني♪
We are finally home.
لقد عدنا إلى المنزل أخيراً.
♪Just stick to the story please♪
♪التزم بالقصة من فضلك♪
♪You say that you want to see me♪
♪تقول إنك تريد رؤيتي♪
♪But truth is scary♪
♪لكن الحقيقة مخيفة♪
♪So here I stand alone♪
♪ها أنا ذا أقف وحيداً♪
Do not move.
لا تتحرك.
You'll tear your wound.
سوف تمزق جرحك.
This way, I will not move and tear the wound.
وبهذه الطريقة، لن أتحرك وأمزق الجرح.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
there is something that has bothered me for days.
هناك شيء ما يزعجني منذ أيام.
When I was on the cliff,
عندما كنت على الجرف،
I vaguely,
بشكل مبهم،
dimly,
بشكل خافت،
saw...
رأى...
a dragon.
تنين.
Did you see it?
هل رأيته؟
That was my dragon.
كان ذلك تنيني.
So this dragon is your baby,
إذن هذا التنين هو طفلك،
like Nan Xing and his octopus?
مثل نان شينغ وأخطبوطه؟
Yes.
نعم.
Your baby is way cuter than you.
طفلكِ أجمل منكِ بكثير.
The one you raised
الشخص الذي ربيته
has a temper just as hard to deal with as yours.
لديه مزاج يصعب التعامل معه تماماً مثلك.
So, where does it usually live?
إذن، أين يعيش عادةً؟
Deep in the mountains and forests.
في أعماق الجبال والغابات.
It is an anomaly, after all.
إنها حالة شاذة، في نهاية المطاف.
Staying away from people is safer,
الابتعاد عن الناس أكثر أماناً.
and it's more comfortable.
وهو أكثر راحة.
But their boy,
لكن ابنهم،
has been quite a loner.
كان شخصًا انطوائيًا إلى حد كبير.
He never smiled or greeted us
لم يبتسم أو يلقي التحية علينا أبداً
whenever he saw us.
كلما رآنا.
Just like they said on the news.
تمامًا كما قالوا في الأخبار.
They will turn crazy.
سيصابون بالجنون.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I am really glad we became
أنا سعيد حقاً لأننا أصبحنا
partners.
شركاء.
Just partners?
مجرد شركاء؟
These past few months have been intense.
لقد كانت الأشهر القليلة الماضية مليئة بالأحداث.
Constant close calls
مواقف خطيرة متكررة
and even
وحتى
entering your dreams.
دخول أحلامك.
I asked my teacher to look into those dreams.
طلبت من معلمي أن يبحث في تلك الأحلام.
In Sunset Forest,
في غابة الغروب،
there is a type of fern
يوجد نوع من السرخس
that releases special molecules
التي تطلق جزيئات خاصة
when fog humidity exceeds 90 percent.
عندما تتجاوز نسبة الرطوبة في الضباب 90 بالمائة.
Anyone who inhales them
أي شخص يستنشقها
will have their brain invaded,
سيتم غزو أدمغتهم،
specifically the areas tied to memory and imagination.
وتحديداً المناطق المرتبطة بالذاكرة والخيال.
That is why our dreams were linked.
ولهذا السبب ارتبطت أحلامنا.
More precisely,
وبشكل أدق،
we shared each other's subconscious.
لقد تقاسمنا اللاوعي الخاص بكل منا.
If it were the subconscious,
لو كان الأمر يتعلق بالعقل الباطن،
then what we experienced in those dreams
ثم ما اختبرناه في تلك الأحلام
could be real memories that actually happened.
قد تكون ذكريات حقيقية حدثت بالفعل.
The day your parents were killed,
في اليوم الذي قُتل فيه والداك،
you saw the killer's back.
لقد رأيت ظهر القاتل.
You also know
أنت تعلم أيضاً
he was with the Special Administration Bureau.
كان يعمل في مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
Yes.
نعم.
All these years,
طوال هذه السنوات،
I have been tracking his identity,
لقد كنت أتعقب هويته،
but I still
لكنني ما زلت
have found no trace of him.
لم نعثر على أي أثر له.
Once we gather all the fragments,
بمجرد أن نجمع كل الشظايا،
I will go with you to find your parents' killer.
سأذهب معك للعثور على قاتل والديك.
But the memory of that day
لكن ذكرى ذلك اليوم
has been reshaped
تم إعادة تشكيلها
by your appearance.
من خلال مظهرك.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪